

SWANN MARTIN

CONTACT INFO

- Avenue Paul Deschanel 63, boîte 5, 1030 Schaerbeek
- ☐ Tél: +32 456 59 60 82
- M swannmartin1988@gmail.com
- Portfolio: <u>swannmartin.xyz</u>
- @swann.martin
- https://github.com/swann-martin
- <u>Driving Licence</u>
- # Fluent in English, French Native Speaker

PROFILE

Web and mobile developer specialised in React and React-Native. I also worked with Angular and Ionic 6. I like TypeScript. I worked on several hybrid apps in a professional environment. I have strong adaptation skills and I am organised. In the past, have worked for years in an English speaking context.

PROJECTS https://github.com/swann-martin

WashatHome

Use React, Redux, axios, Leaflet, node, sass

Burger Shop:

Use React, useState

Sofas:

Use React, React-Router, Sass

Portfolio:

Use React, React-Router, Sass

Weather app:

Flutter, OpenWeather Api

CV Generator:

Symfony, twig, jQuery, CSS

HOBBIES



Climbing



GNU Linux,



Fantasy,SF



WEB | MOBILE DEVELOPER

SKILLS

Main Angular **TypeScript** React/ Sass Native Secondary NEXT. В Next.is Bootstrap Flutter node (s) Back-end Php MariaDB/mySql Node Symfony Other

Organised, Rigourous, Flexible, Reactive, Curious Can do attitude, Decisive

Wordpress

Fiama

Github

EXPERIENCE



[</>] MOBILE & WEB DEVELOPER

Git

Beecoming | Decembre 2021 - Today

- Developping Mobile apps in React Native, Ionic 6/ Angular & React.js
- TypeScript, NodeJS
- Agile, Scrum, GitKraken, Jira, Office 360



SALES REPRESENTATIVE LANGUAGE COURSE

Oxford Intensive School of English | 2014 - 2020

- Managing a booking office in Bordeaux & Lille
- Bookings Average Annual Income 250 000€
- Organized, work in English and French, management

TRAINING

O'CLOCK:

Formation React.JS | Juin 2021 - Août 2021

Training in React.js, Redux.

End of training project de fin de formation : A website to rent your washing machine for money.

Technologies: React, Redux, Node, postGreSql

WEBFORCE 3 BORDEAUX

Certification Dev Web | Jan 2021 - Avril 2021

Certifications professionnelles CNCP (catégorie C):

- Techniques d'intégration Web (front-end) : (HTML / CSS, JavaScript / jQuery, Angular, CMS: Wordpress)
- Techniques de développement Web (back-end) : (MySQL, PHP, Symfony).

End of training project : CV generator website.

Technologies: Symfony/Twig/SQL/CSS

UNIVERSITY OF PORTSMOUTH / PARIS X

Master2 FLE / PGCE MFL | Sept 2011 - Juin 2013

- Double Diploma Master 2 Teaching Modern Foreign Languages UK

LYCÉE MIREILLE GRENET COMPIEGNE

BACCALAUREAT Sciences Engineering technologies spe Electronics with Honors | 2007